[{
        "question": "ques_tech0",
        "answer": "2"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech1",
        "answer": " i=4,j=1 & i=5,j=1"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech2",
        "answer": "[[], [1], [2], [1, 2], [3], [1, 3], [2, 3], [1, 2, 3]]"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech3",
        "answer": " ! printf("
        hello ")"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech4",
        "answer": "printf(" % f % Lf ", a, b);"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech5",
        "answer": "15 GB"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech6",
        "answer": "30 GB"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech7",
        "answer": "ASUS Zenfone 2"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech8",
        "answer": "Oppo "
    } {
        "question": "ques_tech9",
        "answer": "1"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech10",
        "answer": "0"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech11",
        "answer": "10"
    } {
        "question": "ques_tech12",
        "answer": "0 3 4.00"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech13",
        "answer": "Hello Coding"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech14",
        "answer": "3 4 5"
    } {
        "question": "ques_tech15",
        "answer": "It is stored in CPU"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech16",
        "answer": "-8192"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech17",
        "answer": "[0,1,2,3,4,5]"
    } {
        "question": "ques_tech18",
        "answer": "[4,5,6]"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech19",
        "answer": "1,2,34,5,6"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech20",
        "answer": "10"
    } {
        "question": "ques_tech21",
        "answer": "3"

    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech22",
        "answer": "ENDIF"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech23",
        "answer": "Tribonacci series"
    },
    {
        "question": "ques_tech24",
        "answer": "Tests whether a binary tree is a Binary Search Tree"
    },

]